{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "This is the man ______ son is so clever.",
      "a": "who",
      "b": "whom",
      "c": "that",
      "d": "whose",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- \"Whom\" refers to someone who is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- That: used after verbs, nouns, and adjectives to introduce a clause which shows what someone says or thinks, or states a fact or reason ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "______ did you speak to?",
      "a": "What",
      "b": "Which",
      "c": "Who",
      "d": "That",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n-\"Who\" use to ask for person who is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- What/ Which ask for something \n- Can not use \"that\" to ask for subject ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "______ is this pen? It's mine.",
      "a": "What",
      "b": "Whose",
      "c": "Which",
      "d": "Whom",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action)\n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to)\n- \"Whom\"  refers to someone who is  an Object Pronoun (receive an action)\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "That's the girl ______ he fell in love with.",
      "a": "whom",
      "b": "which",
      "c": "whose",
      "d": "of who",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- \"Whom\" refers to someone who is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you know ______ spoke at the meeting?",
      "a": "whom",
      "b": "who",
      "c": "whose",
      "d": "which",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- \"Whom\" refers to someone who is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is the man ______ I saw yesterday.",
      "a": "whose",
      "b": "whom",
      "c": "to who",
      "d": "which",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- \"Whom\" refers to someone who is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The party, ______ we enjoyed so much, ended late.",
      "a": "which",
      "b": "who",
      "c": "whose",
      "d": "whom",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- \"Whom\" refers to someone who is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n- We prefer which when the number of choices is limited ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "This was the party ______ lasted all night.",
      "a": "whose",
      "b": "that",
      "c": "what",
      "d": "whom",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- \"Whom\" refers to someone who is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- What: used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain \n- What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited \n- That: used after verbs, nouns, and adjectives to introduce a clause which shows what someone says or thinks, or states a fact or reason ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "That's the boy ______ came yesterday.",
      "a": "whom",
      "b": "which",
      "c": "who",
      "d": "whose",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n- We prefer which when the number of choices is limited ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "______ did you have lunch with?",
      "a": "Who",
      "b": "That",
      "c": "Which",
      "d": "Whose",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- That: used after verbs, nouns, and adjectives to introduce a clause which shows what someone says or thinks, or states a fact or reason \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n- We prefer which when the number of choices is limited ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}